<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Nebez Briefkani</title><link>https://nebezb.com/</link><description>Recent content on Nebez Briefkani</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nebezb.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Microservice BS</title><link>https://nebezb.com/microservice-bs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nebezb.com/microservice-bs/</guid><description>In the last 5 years, &amp;ldquo;microservice architecture&amp;rdquo; has gone from cool buzzword to dangerous plague rife with misinformation, slipped deadlines, and unquestionably shittier end products.
A misplaced need for microservices drives organizations down the path of blindly scattering the business domain over the network. Production errors that would&amp;rsquo;ve been caught at compile time now arrear at runtime. Feature velocity is exchanged for defects. Every production incident turns into a murder mystery with unhelpful stack traces.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://nebezb.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nebezb.com/about/</guid><description>Canadian-Iraqi software engineer &amp;amp; startup enthusiast based in Vancouver, Canada I&amp;rsquo;ve been developing software for nearly 15 years. Previously Lightspeed, SSENSE, Shopify, co-founder of nukern, LXRandCo, and now-defunct Infantry Online.
Currently Software Engineering Manager at Amazon Web Services where I&amp;rsquo;m building a services marketplace called IQ to connect freelancers, consultants, and fractional CTOs with businesses of all sizes.
After two failed ventures and one successful IPO of an omnichannel retailer, I&amp;rsquo;ve developed a deep expertise in the ecommerce, luxury retail, and payments industries.</description></item></channel></rss>